When you follow your dream, there's no telling what you'll become.
Connie and Carla is a comedy, crime, music film directed by Michael Lembeck.
After accidentally witnessing a mafia hit in the Windy City, gal pals Connie and Carla skip town for
L.A., where they go way undercover as singers working the city's dinner theater circuit ...
disguised as drag queens.
Now, it's not enough that they become big hits on the scene; things get
extra-weird when Connie meets Jeff -- a guy she'd like to be a woman with.
Connie, played by Nia Vardalos.
Carla, played by Toni Collette.
Jeff, played by David Duchovny.
Robert / Peaches, played by Stephen Spinella.
Lee / N'Cream, played by Alec Mapa.
Stanley, played by Ian Gomez.
Connie and Carla is a 2004 American comedy film directed by Michael Lembeck
and starring Nia Vardalos, Toni Collette, and David Duchovny.
The screenplay was written by Vardalos.
The film was shot in Vancouver and featured a number of local drag queens, including Joan-E, Justine
Tyme, Carlotta Gurl, Devana Demille, Seemore Illusion, and Vivian Von BrokenHymen.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, chicago,
illinois, undercover, drag queen, witness.
The tone is lighthearted.